sourcerepo.com 2015-12-26

# privacy

Privacy Policy 

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the sourcerepo.com and Hosting Playground Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Hosting Playground Inc include sourcerepo.com. The Hosting Playground Inc website, sourcerepo,  is a source code hosting service. By using the Hosting Playground Inc website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

Collection of your Personal Information 

Hosting Playground Inc may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Hosting Playground Inc's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Hosting Playground Inc. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Hosting Playground Inc website. 

Hosting Playground Inc encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Hosting Playground Inc so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Hosting Playground Inc is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Hosting Playground Inc website. 

Use of your Personal Information 

Hosting Playground Inc collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

Hosting Playground Inc may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Hosting Playground Inc and its affiliates. Hosting Playground Inc may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

Hosting Playground Inc does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

Hosting Playground Inc may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Hosting Playground Inc, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Hosting Playground Inc will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Hosting Playground Inc or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Hosting Playground Inc; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Hosting Playground Inc, or the public. 

Use of Cookies 

The Hosting Playground Inc website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Hosting Playground Inc pages, or register with Hosting Playground Inc site or services, a cookie helps Hosting Playground Inc to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Hosting Playground Inc website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Hosting Playground Inc features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Hosting Playground Inc services or websites you visit. 

Security of your Personal Information 

Hosting Playground Inc secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Children Under Thirteen 

Hosting Playground Inc does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe 

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Hosting Playground Inc by contacting us here: 

\- Web page: _________________ 

\- Email: _________________ 

\- Phone: _________________ 

Changes to this Statement 

Hosting Playground Inc will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Hosting Playground Inc encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Hosting Playground Inc is protecting your information. 

Contact Information 

Hosting Playground Inc welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Hosting Playground Inc has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Hosting Playground Inc at: 

Hosting Playground Inc 

980 Cipriana Drive Unit A-1 #189 

Myrtle Beach, South Carolina 29572 

Email Address: 

support@sourcerepo.com 

Telephone number: 

8006034125 

Effective as of October 04, 2013
